Feel like trying something new
for dinner?
Maybe Indian? Tex-Mex?
Ever wonder how humans would
be different if they evolved...
_from lizards instead of mammals?
LEONARD:
Okay, let's talk about that.
As you know,
lizards, cold-blooded animals...
...lack the ability to sense temperature.
But they do move more sluggishly
when it's cold.
So lizard weathermen
would say things like:
"Bring a sweater, it's slow outside.”
I love my mind.
We all do. Now, how about dinner?
Oh, I would assume we'd enjoy insects
or smaller lizards.
We could also pull each other's tails off
and grill them. They'll just grow back.
Oh!
My life-size cardboard
Mr. Spock is here.
I know he wouldn't care
for an outburst of human emotion...
...but, oh, goodie, oh, goodie,
oh, goodie.
Commander Spock requesting
permission to be unfolded.
-Excuse me.
-Permission granted, commander.
--which is why the more intelligent
the monkey, the more feces they fling.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Excuse me, Amy.
Uh, Penny, do you have plans for dinner?
-You guys going somewhere?
-No, just you and me.
You mean, like a date?
Not like a date, a date.
AMY & BERNADETTE:
Ooh.
Um....
Okay. Sure.
AMY & BERNADETTE:
Ooh.
Oh, no. They sent the wrong Spock.
Live long and suck it, Zachary Quinto.
This is so exciting. If Leonard
and Penny get back together...
...Howard and I can go
on double dates with them.
How come you never invite
Sheldon and me on a double date?
Uh. ...
How's it going in there, Penny?
PENNY:
Just a sec.
Too much?
-Yes.
-No.
Okay. Just hang on.
You just can't handle her raw sexuality,
can you?
When did you and Leonard break up?
PENNY:
Uh, about two years ago.
Why do you think
he asked you out again?
PENNY: I don't know.
-Maybe he's dying.
That would be so romantic.
PENNY:
He's not dying.
Too bad.
If he were, she could throw him in bed
and ride him right up until he flat lines.
How about this?
-Maybe.
-Come on.
Yeah, okay, no.
Do you think you'll sleep with him
tonight?
PENNY: Absolutely not. We're just gonna have
dinner and, you know, see how it goes.
If he were dying,
would you sleep with him?
PENNY: What?
-Assuming he were dying...
...of something that couldn't
be sexually transmitted.
You know,
like a spear wound to the head.
PENNY:
Okay, he is not dying.
How do you know? Are you a doctor?
You can make-believe though.
Sometimes Howard and I pretend
that his arrhythmia is acting up...
...and I'm a sexy cardiologist...
...and the naughty part is
I'm not in his HMO network.
Screw it. I'm not gonna make
a big deal out of this. It's just dinner.
With a dead man. Rawr.
Amy, stop It.
Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
Relax. You know Leonard’s always been
crazy about you. It's gonna be great.
We've finally gotten to a place where
we can hang out without it being weird.
-If something goes wrong, then what?
-It'll just be Sheldon and me...
...going on a double date
with Howard and Bernadette.
Sure. We'd love that.
Change your clothes,
we got a lot riding on this.
Hmm.
I want to build a road,
but I need wood.
Do either of you fellows have wood?
[SNICKERING]
I don't understand the laughter.
The object of Settlers of Catan
is to build roads and settlements. ..
...to do so requires wood.
Now, I have sheep, I need wood.
Who has wood for my sheep?
[LAUGHING]
Okay. How do I look?
More to the point,
why are you doing this?
-What are you talking about?
-You forget what Penny did to you?
It took you two years and defiling my
sister to turn that frown upside down.
I didn't defile your sister,
we had a relationship.
I heard you call her Brown Sugar.
In my book that's defilement.
-You wanna know my opinion?
-Oh, boy, do I.
Sarcasm?
No.
All right, then.
The reason you're fixated on
a good-natured simpleton like Penny...
...Is that she's the exact opposite
of your first romantic attachment...
...your brilliant, yet intimidating,
mother.
Where on earth did you get that from?
It's in her book
Needy Baby, Greedy Baby.
That doesn't make it true.
It's called non-fiction for a reason,
Leonard.
See you later.
If they make a movie version
of that book. ..
...you know who should play
Leonard's mother? Sandra Bullock.
-Why?
-Because she's great in everything.
Now, where were we? Oh, yes.
Does anyone have any wood?
[SNICKERING]
Come on. I just want wood.
Why are you making it so hard?
[LAUGHING]
[LAUGHS]
So do they have a name for a first date
with someone you used to go out with?
That's a good question.
How about "awkward"?
-Yeah, that sounds right.
-Yeah? Heh, heh.
How about if we pretend we're actually
on a first date? See how that goes.
Okay.
So, Polly, tell me about yourself.
-Heh, heh. It's Penny.
-Oh, sorry. Yeah. Awkward.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, let's see. I'm from Nebraska,
and ever since I was a little girl...
...| dreamed of moving to L.A.
and becoming a movie star.
Anyway, after four years
of acting lessons and waiting tables...
...I've done a hemorrhoid
commercial...
...and a production of Anne Frank
above a bowling alley.
So you know, dreams do come true.
-Your turn.
-Uh, let's see. Ahem. Uh....
I am an experimental physicist
at Caltech.
Most of my research
is with high-powered lasers, and--
Oh, I've just gotten
a big government grant...
...to see if they can be used
to knock out incoming ballistic missiles.
-Wow. Can they?
-Oh, God, no.
[LAUGHS]
But the money's pretty good.
And I used the equipment
to make my own Bat-Signal.
[LAUGHS]
Bat-Signal?
What are you, some kind of nerd?
Not some kind of nerd,
I am the king of nerds.
[LAUGHING]
-What does that mean?
-It means if anyone displeases me...
...I don't help them set up their printer.
[LAUGHS]
You are so funny.
Good. Remember that
when I take my shirt off.
-This is nice. I'm so glad we did this.
-Me too.
So, what do you think,
are we gonna get back together?
Whoa, not so fast.
I'm sorry, what did I say?
Leonard, you know I will always
have feelings for you--
-Oh, God.
“What?
You said "always."
You'll always have feelings for me.
-So?
-That sounds like something you'd say...
...If you didn't want a relationship
with someone.
"This isn't working out,
but I'll always have feelings for you."
"I'm sorry I slept with your best friend,
"Here's the thing, Lisa,
I'm into dudes now...
...but I'll always have feelings
for you."
-How would you say it?
- I have feelings for you.
-Same thing.
-No, it's not. "Always" made it worse.
-You're over-thinking this.
-No, I'm not.
-You always over-think things.
-There you go. "Always" made it worse.
See, this is where everything
goes wrong, when we talk.
Well, I don't know how you have
a relationship without talking.
I went out with T.J. for eight months.
We never talked.
To this day, I don't even know
what T.J. stands for.
Wait, if you guys didn't talk--?
Never mind, stupid question.
And now that I have some wood. ..
...I'm going to begin the erection
of my settlement.
He's got to be doing this on purpose.
Ooh, eight-thirty. You and Penny decide
to go out and paint the town beige?
You're 30 years old
and you live with your mother.
I guess it didn't go well.
We don't know that. Not to a certainty.
All we know is that Leonard is home.
[LEONARD SCREAMS]
How about now?
Again, not enough evidence.
For all we know, he's being murdered.
Now, back to our game.
You were in the middle of an erection.
[SNICKERS]
Oh, of course.
It's right here in my hand.
[PHONE BEEPS]
What does she want from me now??
-What's up?
-Do not over-think this.
- I don't understand--
-Bup, bup, bup.
-Okay, but earlier it seemed like--
-No talking.
LEONARD: Even during?
Because sometimes I have questions.
[BOTH PANTING]
Well, that was fun.
Yeah. Except for when
I got the foot cramp.
You hung in there though.
There was a lot at stake.
So, what do you wanna do now?
Well, I wanna go get my asthma inhaler,
but it might ruin the moment.
So help me out, here.
How does a miserable date end in sex?
I don't know, it's complicated.
I'm pretty smart guy, and right now my
brain has dibs on the blood supply...
...So give it a go.
Okay. It's just--
At that restaurant when you said
you wanted us to be together again...
...It got very real, very fast
and I panicked.
Why? What are you afraid of?
Well, what if we do go out and I do
something stupid and dump you again?
What if I dump you?
[PENNY SCOFFS]
Come on, be serious.
Well, how about if we don't think
about this as a relationship?
It could be more like
a new version of software.
Penny and Leonard 2.0.
We can test it internally,
shake out the bugs...
...and if we both feel it's solid,
then we'll roll it out to the public.
We don't tell people
we're back together?
Exactly.
We pretend like our date went badly.
Well, we don't really have to pretend.
And we let them think that we decided
to just be friends...
...and that everything's cool.
Okay. Great.
Hey, I just remembered.
I still got one of your inhalers.
I can't believe you kept this.
I was gonna throw it away,
but I just couldn't.
That is so sweet.
Heh.
In 25 to 30 minutes I'm gonna show you
how much this means to me.
-Leonard?
-Yeah, hi.
How's it going?
Can't complain, thanks for asking.
What were you doing out
at 3:00 in the morning?
Well-- What are you doing up?
I was using the bathroom.
Yeah, well, so was I.
Really? I didn't see you in there.
Obviously.
When I saw that you were in ours,
I went and used another one.
Where?
Uh, the gas station across the street.
-In your pajamas?
Yes.
Without shoes?
On a cold winter's night?
Yes.
That seems unlikely.
Did you bring your asthma inhaler?
Uh, uh, yes, I did.
Well, then I guess it's plausible.
-Hang on a second, mister.
“What?
After you used the facilities at the gas
station, did you make a purchase?
What?
It's customary when using the restroom
at a retail establishment. ..
...to make a small purchase. Did you?
No.
Here's $2.
Go buy some beef jerky.
I don't want beef jerky.
It's not about you.
It's about a poor immigrant
from Pakistan...
...frying to make his way in America
by working the graveyard shift...
_at the Colorado Boulevard Chevron.
Fine.
Needy baby, greedy baby, indeed.
Leonard will be here in a moment.
He's looking for
a different parking space.
-Why?
“We were next to a car with an...
... .ask me about my grandchildren”
bumper sticker...
...and I was afraid if we ran into them
on the way out, I'd be obligated to do so.
I'm so disappointed
it didn't work with him and Penny.
Me too. Out of deference to them,
let's not flaunt our happy relationship.
You have a keen insight into
the human heart, Amy Farrah Fowler.
We are next to a Subaru
with a Gore-Lieberman bumper sticker.
Well, I doubt they'd wanna
talk about that, so we're fine.
I'm surprised to see you here
after it went so badly with Penny.
Well, hey, we're grown-ups.
We can still be friends.
Boy, I don't know if I could be friends
with Howie if we broke up.
-Why not?
-I'm a very vengeful person.
-Really?
-With access to weaponized smallpox.
Let me get you some water. You need
menus, or you know what you want?
Leonard knows what he wants, but it
looks like he's not gonna get it from you.
-Howard.
-No, that's okay, Bernadette.
Sometimes these things
just don't work out.
Yeah. It's all good. We'll always
have feelings for each other.
Oh. That's nice.
See? She knew what "always" meant.
Wow, you're like a dog with a bone,
aren't you?
-I'm just making a point.
-Is the point you don't know...
-...when to let something go?
-People, people, please.
Before you say something
you both regret...
...I'd like to place my order.
Yeah, hang on, Sheldon.
You know why we can't be together?
-Because you always have to be right.
-That is not true.
I gotta go with Leonard on this.
He is wrong more than anyone I know.
You know what, I just realized
I'm on a break. I'll get someone else.
Promise me
when our new waitress comes over. ..
...you will not start a complicated,
on-again, off-again relationship with her.
Because I'm very, very hungry.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Unbelievable.
Mind explaining why you were being
a jerk at the restaurant?
I was trying to act like we weren't
seeing each other. That was the plan.
The plan was to tell people
we decided to stay friends.
But that's a little hard to do when
you're always being such a tool bag.
I don't have to stand here
and take this crap.
Where do you think you're going?
Isn't sex after fighting
kind of what we do now?
Yeah, kind of, yeah.
-What are we doing?
-What do you mean?
Every scenario I play out
for you and me ends badly.
Because you over-think everything.
SHELDON:
Leonard, are you listening to me?
-What? Yeah.
-This is a disaster.
I distinctly ordered the Leonard Nimoy
Mr. Spock cardboard standee.
Why would I feel safer with
Zachary Quinto at the foot of my bed?
I don't know.
He was pretty badass on Heroes.
You're right. I'll give him a shot.
Hang on.
-Penny, you have plans for dinner?
-You guys going somewhere?
No, I mean just you and me.
AMY & BERNADETTE:
Ooh.
Have you thought this through?
Yes. And I think we should go anyway.
No, can't do it.
Sorry, Quinto, you're going back.
If you and Leonard get back together,
Sheldon and I will finally have...
-...someone to go on double dates with.
“What about me and Howard?
Fine, we can double with you too.
So insecure.
Where are you guys going to eat?
Penny?
Do you, Penny, take Leonard
to be your lawful wedded husband?
Well, it's a little late for me
to start saying "no," isn't it?
AMY:
Penny?
Sorry. I just remembered
I've got to stop by the drugstore.
[English - US - SDH]